A very good evening friends Vyapak with
another set of questions today's last
question is are you otherwise Kasana Ann
list start with art last question
of the day is the question on screen is
you are driving and improve yourself what will you do
to driving in wrong
direction cheetal worker recruit get angry habit
traffic constable Arvind with
up industrial so as you saw
if you turn right and you reach but 92 what will
you do what problem
and will you go in the wrong direction on the
side or will you take another long but right
route or will you pick up quantity then
quantity because you will start driving or
you will see pedestrians walking on the road and
people will start arguing with them so you have to choose
one correct answer and that is the correct answer it can make
you win very
exciting gifts as we
told you today is the second day of our show
we are on dec20  But I showed five questions
every 2 hours, you can participate in it
and interesting Patils that
you can participate in five questions of daily benefit every day
and
win trust relief exciting, so there is no
such person who if you do not
participate in the post once or in mixed form,
you can participate in all
and you can be a part of this quiz contest,
come for this contest,
this fight is an awareness
program regarding road safety,
now I will tell you more important in this that
how can we make our Indian roads clear
for everyone and you can
also participate in this mask job movie of ours, you
can join us, you can be a
partner somewhere in making our viewers,
so come with your family,
with your friends, you can participate in it
and now you can get a chance to win many prizes,
as you can see,
you are seeing the questions on my screen  Yes,
you are driving and approach the road, then
you will drive in the wrong direction, check
long, definitely have the habit of crossing the road, Traffic
Constable Arvind with Strangers said that
we have seen that this is very common
in people that when you come, you are
very tired,
you have too much fresh air, it is
very hot or you are
not able to sleep properly due to which you
work daily at night club, it is troubling you the next day,
you are well, on one hand the tiredness
remains in you, then somewhere or the other it becomes a
cause of frustration for people, or if
you leave home late and you have to
reach on time and you get a job
or anything like this happens, then
what happens, it becomes a real reason for you,
express comes upon you due to
which people often make mistakes,
or in our hurry to leave the road, we do
not see the way,
which in itself
creates a problem where we are the reason
and that jam is a coffin, to get out of that jam,
where you  And it means that in
order to save some time, you end up packing the entire vehicle
and sometimes it takes you 2 hours to get
out of the train. So do
n't take too much credit for yourself.
If you feel that
you are feeling a little tired
or something else without a driver, then also suggest that
you don't drive now. Or
if there is any vibration on your side, you
can try it, tell them to dry off
and you can sit on the side and rest. This is very
important
because if a person is
stressed, then the chances of an accident
increase. Sometimes, due to lack of sleep,
you fall asleep on the way.
Avoid such things, it can save you to a great extent.
If we
remain aware, then we can make our day easier.
[Music] It must be
Avni. Sometimes when people get angry, are frustrated, or are upset, then it harms
others.  They start driving over and the
quantity of thoughts that stand since morning to
help you,
people start shouting at them and
because of traffic jams, because of all these things,
we have to keep a little patience on the route, a
little patience, we have to work
and just like we drive, the
routes that you are using on the way may
not be for you, they are
all common roads for everyone, so you have to be a little
careful that it is not only for you but for
others as well, constable driver,
then give way to the driver,
stop your car before crossing the crossing, this is very important and it is
very important to follow all the road safety rules, I request
you all to
follow all the road safety rules, meanwhile wear a
helmet, which is very important,
people do this because we travel on roads every day, have
you ever heard of the 1 inch
rule, what is Kittu skin necessary, then
I would like to tell you my system that the 1 inch
skin rule is now  In India, if
we
change our behavior a little bit from the settings and the driving that happens in India, this slip side, bumper driving, then somewhere or the other
we have the issue of traffic jam, the
issue of getting stuck in the acid,
we can ignore all these things,
if we follow the rules of
acceptance, but we will follow that, if we drive
in a distance by
joining the seats, that in
case if someone
applies emergency brakes, then there should be enough difference between your car and their car or the one
next to you so that you
can apply safe brakes, so it is more important
that you should follow rule 216, now let's talk about
our road
safety related, you can see it, it is
visible on my screen, which is
going on in this contest, now this is our
last question of today, you can participate in it,
it will be visible for two hours,
after that your voting will be closed,
you will not be able to vote and you
too, as much as you  The sooner you
participate in this, the more benefit you will get.
Not only you, your family,
your friends, everyone
can participate in this.
I will give you a question again.
If you are driving and
approach any road, you will drive in the wrong
direction and get angry with strangers.
Then
you decide what you will do and you
can give us your answer. If your
answer is correct, then you have a chance to take a
very exciting gift for yourself, your
family members, your village and to
become a lesson in this safety camp of ours. You can also make our day happy somewhere.
This is what has happened that you have come to the
last camp and join this campaign by Gautam
Dubai. By migrating the answer of this question, you can
participate in the fifth question
and the most interesting thing is that you can
participate in all the five of the Pandu.
Yes and its results will be
displayed on daily basis, the
results will be announced in our last
night's show,
speaking of plants, the results will be
announced in our questions, okay, so
you can see it, it
comes on our life theme, you can check it by going to our channel and you
can check about your result by going to our website
and we will request you to
participate every day, it will continue till 18th February
and you have a
chance to
win exciting prizes like this, it is a
part of the best of all
that a correct answer can bring you happiness
in your life and this entire campaign is
very important for you and your entire family's safety, you must be very careful, this is completely
related to road safety,
our theme is on road safety, we
want you, your loved ones, your family members,
friends, everyone to stay safe every day
So we would request you to
follow the rules of all the sets believed in the entire universe, be a
little cooperative with our traffic policemen,
like you
plant trees, there is a speed limit here or else the
thing about wearing a helmet, if you
follow it then it is not for anyone else but for
you, it is for your safety, the one in
quick solution is very important,
it creates a layer,
if something happens in front of you in the middle of this game or office,
it saves you, it
saves your screen from any big accident, it
saves your head, any request is that
if someone happens to you, be it
your wife, your children
or anyone else, they should also wear helmets
and the most important thing is
that the helmets come back,
buy only Sai Maa's helmets, do
not buy local ones because there is
no benefit from them, come let's say Sai Maa's
helmets are made for safety purposes
and are the best for you,
they save you from becoming a victim of any accident.  You
can do anything if I give it to you, then it can
save your head from getting damaged.
I also requested that whenever you buy a helmet, always
buy ISI marked one and the
size of your helmet is a very good
benefit for you. It should be PU fitted. It should
not be used much. If it is
used too much, then if
something happens and you fall, it will come out and
separate and if it is tight, then it will be
uncomfortable for you. While
driving, I also request you to always
buy a helmet of your size. Be it children or already
aged, you should
buy ISI marked helmet for all of them and buy that helmet which fits them, it will
save your head from any accident. So Vikram Baat viewers, here
you are seeing the question on the screen,
come and join, know about road safety, know
new things,
join us and make our day better. So
once again I am putting
this question for you, you are driving,
approve way, you  Will live in wrong
direction take long and roots get
angry ginger traffic constable or and
going with the distance so what will you do you
can decide you and us
can win exciting prizes between the correct answers
Ajay
that Nitin Bhaiya part of this change which we
want to bring on everyday if and till one that
if we all change then the country will change jeans
tops with 10th
that with this
I
want to say thank you for staying with me that I
salwar loss happened that so much fun with I don't
10 questions you some tips
telecast you thank you so much u